https://www.pharm-int.com/privacy-policy/

MenuHome$100,000 Grant About AboutLeadershipSubject Matter ExpertsAwardsCareer ResourcesResourcesArticlesCase StudiesVideos and PodcastsBrochuresPress ReleasesTradeshowsContactCOVID-19Concept to Clinic to CommercializationDosage Forms FormulationFormulationHighly Potent Api Aseptic FillingAseptic FillingAST Parenteral Drug DevelopmentParenteral Drug and Injectable ProcessingLyophilizationClinical Trial ManagementFD&C 503BCommercial ManufacturingCommercial ManufacturingSerializationEquipment ListAnalytical & Quality AssuranceAnalytical & Quality AssuranceQuality AssuranceRegulatory Support
Sign Up Now for Our Newsletter: "The Pii Formula" and gain valuable insights   Subscribe PRIVACY POLICYBefore using Pharmaceutics International, Inc (Pii) Sites, please read this Privacy Policy carefully.We at Pharmaceutics International, Inc (Pii) respect your privacy and are committed to reasonable measures to safeguard any personal information you may share with us. The purpose of this privacy policy and agreement (the “Privacy Policy”) is to set out the principles governing our use of your personal information.This Privacy Policy does not cover any interaction you may have with us by telephone, postal mail, or other offline communications. It applies to the gathering and use of information on this site and other sites (collectively, the “Pii’s Sites”) operated by Pharmaceutics International, Inc (Pii).By visiting Pii’s Sites, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, please do not pursue the use of Pii Sites; your continued use of Pii’s Sites will be interpreted as your acceptance of its terms and conditions.Information that we collect Personal informationGenerally, you are not required to register yourself to access Pii’s Sites; however, at various locations on PII’s Sites, we may request that you supply us with “personal information”, such as your name, email address, mailing address and telephone number. This will be the case if you want us to provide you with additional information about our services. You will always know when we are collecting personal information because we only collect personal information when you voluntarily submit it to us. If you do choose to give us personal information through Pii’s Sites, we will collect and retain that information, and you consent to the transfer and storage of that information on our servers. If you choose not to give us personal information, we may not be able to provide you with services you may request or require.Non-personal informationWhen you use Pii’s Sites, we may also collect “non-personal information”, which is information that, by itself, cannot be used to identify or contact you, such as technical information (like your IP address, the type of browser you are using, the websites you visit immediately before and immediately after you visit Pii’s Sites, and other anonymous data involving your use of Pii’s Sites). Non-personal information may also include information that you provide us through your use of Pii’s Sites, such as the terms you enter into the search functions of Pii’s Sites.Individuals under the age of majorityPii’s Sites are not intended for or designed to attract individuals under the age of majority. We do not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from persons under the age of majority and as such, we do not knowingly allow them to seek information on Pii’s Sites.How we use the information we collect Our services and Pii’s SitesWe use your personal information to provide you any services that you may request or require, to communicate with you, to allow you to make a proper assessment of our services, to allow us to process applications and share periodic industry-related information. We will never use your personal information in ways unrelated to the foregoing. We use the non-personal information we collect to analyze how Pii’s Sites are being used, and to improve the content of Pii’s Sites, and marketing and promotional efforts.Email communications and opting outIf you send us an email with questions or comments, we may use your personal information to respond to your questions or comments, and we may save your questions or comments for future reference. There may be times when you will have the opportunity to subscribe to an email list or electronic newsletter that will send information about Pii’s Sites to your email address. However, we will provide you with the option to change your preferences and opt-out of receiving those communications by clicking the “unsubscribe” link included in the email. If you unsubscribe, we will make reasonable efforts to discontinue these email communications as soon as practicable. We may also, from time to time, contact you by e-mail with unsolicited information about our services. If you do not wish to receive such e-mails you can easily opt out by sending us an email.Disclosure of information to third parties Affiliates and non-affiliatesExcept as specifically set forth in this Privacy Policy, we do not share your personal information with any non-affiliated third party without your permission. We may share your personal information with certain entities that control us, are controlled by us, or are under common control with us (our “Affiliates”), and websites operated by our Affiliates or other businesses of Pii, so that they and we can offer you services that may be of interest to you.Other disclosuresWe could disclose personal information if required or requested to do so to comply with legal requirements such as a law, regulation, warrant, subpoena, court order or other government or law enforcement authority or regulatory agency, to enforce or apply our rights and agreements, or when we believe in good faith that disclosing this information is necessary or advisable, including, for example, to protect the rights, property, or safety of our businesses, Pii’s Sites, our customers, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other corporate entities and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction. We reserve the right to use or disclose non-personal information in any way we see fit.Notice and choice for onward transferWe will ask you for your opt-in consent to share your personal information with a third party for any other reason.Security of the information we collectThe security of your personal information is important to us. We maintain physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards to secure your personal information. However, there is always some risk in transmitting information electronically. As we deem appropriate, we use security measures consistent with industry standards. However, we cannot guarantee the security of our databases, nor can we guarantee that information you supply won’t be intercepted while being transmitted to us over the Internet. Of course, any information you post to any message board, discussion group, or other public posting area on Pii’s Sites is available to anyone with Internet access.Questions and requests regarding the information we collectAny questions you may have regarding our Privacy Policy, the accuracy of your personal information or the use of your personal information, or any requests that we correct, update, or remove your information in our databases, should be directed via email at bd@pharm-int.com or phone at 410-584-0001. Upon receipt of a request to change your information, we will take reasonable steps to verify your identity before granting access or making corrections. After receiving a request to change your information, we will make reasonable efforts to ensure that all of your personal information stored in databases we actively use will be updated as soon as reasonably practicable. However, we reserve the right to retain in our archival files any information we remove from or change in our active website databases. In addition, it is not technologically possible to remove each and every record of the information you have provided to us. A copy of your personal information may exist in a non-erasable form that will be difficult or impossible for us to locate.Third-party linkPii’s Sites may provide links to other third-party Web sites that are outside our control and not covered by this Privacy Policy. We encourage you to review the privacy policies posted on these sites.ChangesWe reserve the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time and will post on this page any changes to this Privacy Policy as soon as they go into effect. Please refer back from time to time to this Privacy Policy on a regular basis to ensure you are aware of the current Privacy Policy.Effective DateThis Privacy Policy is effective as of April 2020.What can we help you with?
×
×
We use cookies to improve your experience. By continuing to browse the site, you are agreeing to our use of cookies. View Cookie settings Accept CookiePrivacy & Cookies Policy
Close Privacy OverviewThis website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these cookies, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may have an effect on your browsing experience.
Necessary
Always EnabledNecessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. This category only includes cookies that ensures basic functionalities and security features of the website. These cookies do not store any personal information.
Non-necessary
Non-necessaryAny cookies that may not be particularly necessary for the website to function and is used specifically to collect user personal data via analytics, ads, other embedded contents are termed as non-necessary cookies. It is mandatory to procure user consent prior to running these cookies on your website.
